thestore.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy | THE STORE

THANK YOU FOR VISITING THESTORE.COM. YOU MADE THE RIGHT CHOICE AND WE WELCOME YOU HERE AND HOPE THAT YOU WILL ENJOY YOUR EXPERIENCE WITH THESTORE. BEFORE YOU BEGIN YOUR WONDERFUL JOURNEY, PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY AS THEY DESCRIBE HOW WE CARE AND PROTECT YOUR PRIVATE INFORMATION.

### PART 1: INTRODUCTION

This is the official Privacy Policy (the "Policy") for www.TheStore.com ("Site," "we," "us,", "our", “ours”, “Platform” or “TheStore”), a website offered in cooperation or connection with TheStore, Inc. 

TheStore is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. The following Policy, describes how TheStore collects and treats personal information. By using the Site you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Policy, terms used in this Policy have the same meanings as in our TheStore Terms of Service, accessible at our Site. As used in this Policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our Affiliates within the United States or internationally. We take your privacy seriously. We are providing this Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information on our Site. We also want to inform you about your choices regarding information. 

### PART 2: INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION

When you visit our Site, we may collect certain non-personal information such as your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, pages you visit, type of browser and operating system you are using. When you register or login with TheStore, we may also collect the personal information that you submit such as but not limited to your name, age, gender, address, email address, country of origin ("Registration Information").

We may also collect non-Registration Information from our users, including the number of downloads on the Site, metadata found in comments or captions from the user and profile changes.

We may use “cookies” to better facilitate the use of our online and mobile environments. You may remove or block cookies using your browser settings, but this may also negatively impact your ability to use our Platform. For example, you may have difficulty logging in or using certain interactive features of our Site.

TheStore may utilize Non-Personal Information, i.e. data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual, for certain general purposes such as to customize content and advertising, improve services, provide generic research and reporting to internal parties. The following are some examples of the Non-Personal Information: individual behavior, location, gender, age, friend’s behavior and connection, etc. Non-Personal Information will never be handed out, reported or otherwise transmitted to external parties without your permission.

We collect information that you voluntarily provide to become a registered User of our Site, and when you use certain aspects of our Site (e.g., entering an email address on a form to send an email from your TheStore account).

We collect information when you register to join TheStore by logging into an account that you already have with certain third-party social networking Sites (“SNS”) (including, but not limited to, Facebook and Twitter) via our Site. For example, our Site allows you to create an account and login to the Site using your Facebook account credentials through Facebook Connect. If you are not currently registered as a user on the Site and you click on “Sign in Using Facebook,” you will first be asked to enter your Facebook credentials and then be given the option to register and join TheStore.

TheStore may sell, share, or trade Non-Personal Information about the users, including and not limited to age, gender, location, occupation, time zone, language, zip code, area code, etc., for statistical purposes. Each user has choice to agree or decline to use the user’s Non-Personal Information for statistical purposes. The user can always change their decision through settings available at the user’s profile.

TheStore does not sell, trade or share your personally identifiable information with third parties unless we obtain your permission first unless such use is under the following circumstances: 

  * Verify a user’s identity for security purposes.
  * Create and manage your account.
  * Provide customer service.
  * Present services or offers that may be of interest to you.
  * Monitor our users' downloads and changes in profiles.
  * To communicate with you about your transactions, new products and services.
  * To improve the quality and design of the Site and any mobile Platforms.
  * When required by law.
  * As part of a business transaction, such as a merger or acquisition by another company.

When you register with us through the Platform to become a registered user of TheStore, we will ask you for certain information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, gender, profile photo, free-form biography, location/hometown, website and email address. If you decide to create your User account by logging into a SNS via the Site, you are using the Personal Information you have already provided to the SNS (such as your “real” name, email address and other information you make publicly available via the SNS) to create your User account on our Site; the information we collect may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNS, so please consult the SNS’s privacy and data practices. For example, by using Facebook Connect, you are allowing TheStore to access the Personal Information in your Facebook account pursuant to the Facebook Terms of Use regarding your use of the Site via Facebook.

We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your “Non-Personal Information,” see below) to provide the Site to you. For example: 

  * We create your user account for your use of the Site based upon the Personal Information you provide.
  * We may use your Personal Information to contact you with TheStore newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or update your “preferences” information in your account settings.

### PART 3: HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

As a valued customer, we recognize that protecting your privacy is important to you. For this reason, TheStore is committed to protecting your personal information in several ways. Only a select number of authorized personnel are authorized to access our servers. Your Registration Information is protected by a unique customer password and user ID, and your password is encrypted. You should not disclose your password information to anyone and you should always remember to log off if using a shared computer. We may retain your personal information for as long as it is required to fulfill our business objective and for as long as it is required by legal requirements. If the user logins to the Site through 3rd party sites such as Facebook, Twitter, and the like, the user is subject to and bound by privacy policies and terms of the 3rd party sites.

Additionally, the personal information collected by TheStore may be stored and processed in a country other than your home country, and such other country may have privacy laws that are less protective than those in effect in your home country. By providing us with your personal information and using the Site, you are consenting to any such transfer of information outside of your home country.

We have taken certain security protections in safeguarding your personal information. However, as with most electronic transactions, no method is 100% safe. While we strive to use a commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its security. Therefore, TheStore assumes no liability regarding the theft, loss, alteration or misuse of personal or other information, including without limitation such information that we have provided to third parties, or with regards to the failure of a third party to abide by the privacy policy or agreement between TheStore and a third party.

### PART 4: INFORMATION SECURITY

We care about the security of your information. We use commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of information collected and maintained through the Site. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us or guarantee that information on the Site may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by unauthorized persons.

### PART 5: PHISHING

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to TheStore. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not request your credit card information, login information, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the US Federal Trade Commission’s website.

### PART 6: BREACH NOTIFICATION

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

### PART 7: INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER

Your information may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, TheStore transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

### PART 8: YOUR CHOICE

If your information is entered into our Site directly (which does not include Login through Facebook), you may opt out of receiving our newsletters when you register with TheStore. By opting out, you will no longer receive certain special offers or promotions. We may continue to send you any legally required notifications and certain notifications, including but not limited to service related notices or notices regarding a change to any of TheStore's policies ("Required Notices"). For example, we may send you a notice regarding server problems or scheduled website maintenance.

### PART 9: OTHER SOCIAL NETWORKING SITES

If you interact with other social networking Sites like Facebook and Twitter, your personal information shared and your information will be governed by the policies of those other service providers.

### PART 10: CHILDREN UNDER AGE OF 13

THESTORE DOES NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13. IF YOU ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 13, YOU MUST NOT USE THIS WEBSITE OR ANY RELATED APPLICATIONS. PLEASE DO NOT SEND PERSONAL INFORMATION INCLUDING YOUR EMAIL, NAME AND/OR CONTACT INFORMATION. ANY CONTACT WITH THESTORE MUST ONLY OCCUR THROUGH YOUR PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN.   IF WE LEARN THAT INFORMATION HAS BEEN COLLECTED FROM SOMEONE UNDER THE AGE OF 13, WE WILL DELETE IT AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.  WE STRONGLY ENCOURAGE OTHERS TO INFORM US OF ANYONE ON THE SITE THAT IS UNDER THE AGE OF 13.

### PART 11: EMAILING VIA THESTORE ACCOUNT AND SHARE ON FACEBOOK

As part of the Site, TheStore Users may communicate with other registered and non-registered Users through use of their TheStore accounts. Where Users have selected the option of adding one or more email addresses to an online form, the message they create in the corresponding template will be sent from TheStore to those email addresses on their behalf.

We may also convert your information into anonymous data in order to help us monitor traffic on our Site. We may also use the Personal Information disclosed to us to assist you with any technical issues you may experience while using our Site. We do not share your Personal Information and the demographic information we have collected with our third party service providers, unless you agreed to it.

Any comment or other content that you post publicly becomes published content and is no longer considered personally identifiable information subject to this Policy.

### PART 12: DISCLOSURES

On rare occasions, TheStore may be required to disclose your Personal Information due to legal or regulatory requirements. In such instances, we reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required in order to comply with TheStore's legal obligations, including but not limited to, complying with court orders, warrants, subpoenas, service of process requirements, or discovery requests.

### PART 13:NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

We reserve the right to change this Policy from time to time, and at our sole discretion. You should make note of the "last updated date" at the beginning of this Policy. With this information, you should be able to identify if the Policy has been updated recently.

Please note that if you have limited your account preferences, we will not change your preferences without your consent. If substantially all of TheStore's assets are sold or merged with another company, TheStore will notify you of the transaction. The acquiring company will be given access to your personal information without your consent. If TheStore sells only a part of its business, the acquiring entity will have access to your personal information without your consent and TheStore may send you a notice regarding this sale.

### PART 14: CONTEST AND SURVEYS

If you enter a contest or complete a survey, we ask may ask you for Personal Information such as your name, address, gender and email address so we can administer the contest and notify the winners.

### PART 15: CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

TheStore, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Officer

### PART 16: DISPUTES

You will resolve any claim, cause of action or dispute (claim) you have with us arising out of or relating to this Policy or TheStore exclusively in a state or federal court located in New York County. The laws of the State of Florida will govern this Policy, as well as any claim that might arise between you and us, without relevant conflict of law provisions. You agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts located in for the purpose of litigating all such claims.

If anyone brings a claim against us related to your actions, content or information on TheStore, you will indemnify and hold us harmless from and against all damages, losses, and expenses of any kind (including reasonable legal fees and costs) related to such claim. Although we provide rules for user conduct, we do not control or direct users' actions on TheStore and are not responsible for the content or information users transmit or share on TheStore. We are not responsible for any offensive, inappropriate, obscene, unlawful or otherwise objectionable content or information you may encounter on TheStore. We are not responsible for the conduct, whether online or offline, or any user of TheStore.

If any provision of the Policy, or the application thereof to any person, place or circumstance, shall be held by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, void or otherwise unenforceable, such provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent possible, or, if incapable of such enforcement, shall be deemed to be deleted from the Policy, and the remainder of the Policy and such provisions as applied to other persons, places and circumstances shall remain in full force and effect.  
This Terms of Privacy Policy was last modified on the date indicated below and is effective immediately. Copyright © 2015 TheStore, Inc. and TheStore.com. This Policy was written in English (US). To the extent any translated version of this agreement conflicts with the English version, the English version controls.

Date of Last Revision: May 07, 2015.
